onebigphoto.com 2013-05-12

# privacy policy » One Big Photo | One Big Photo

**OneBigPhoto.com** has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site.

**You Want Your Photo To Be Removed?**  
We use photographs sent by our visitors, if you found your photo here and you want photo to be removed please [contact us](http://onebigphoto.com/contact-us/) immediately with URL where your photo is located.

**Photos are not for sale!**  
We don’t own rights for photos and we don’t sell prints.

**Third Party Advertising**  
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see [Opt Out of Behavioral Advertising](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

**Third Party Cookies**  
In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique “cookie” on your browser.

**Personal Information**  
We do not share any personal information with any third parties nor do we use any personal information for any purposes.

**External Links**  
This site contains links to other sites. **OneBigPhoto.com** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

**Contacting the Web Site**  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can [contact us](http://onebigphoto.com/contact-us/).
